Guide to the de Caro, Mulvehill and Menkhoff Family Papers 1880-2001 MS 2956
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
de Caro, Mulvehill, and Menkhoff Family Papers
Bulk, 1910-1950
1880-2001
MS 2956
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
2.5 Linear feet 5 manuscript boxes
This collection contains a small selection of documents and photographs of three families of European immigrants who settled in New York City in the late 19th century. These families became connected through a series of marriages and their papers relate to a wide range of topics including marriage and courtship, the Italian-American community in New York City, Columbus Day, and travel accounts.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open to qualified researchers.
Photocopying undertaken by staff only. Limited to twenty exposures of stable, unbound material per day. (Researchers may not accrue unused copy amounts from previous days.)
Items that include presidential signatures will be presented to researchers in duplicate form.
Biographical/Historical note
The de Caros, Menkhoffs, and Mulvehills were three families of European immigrants who settled in New York and Brooklyn in the late 19th century, and eventually became connected through marriage.
Frank A. de Caro immigrated to the United States from Italy in 1884. He worked as a tailor and owned store that manufactured flags, uniforms, and banners. His company De Caro & D’Angelo Co. operated out of a storefront at 169-171 Grand Street in Manhattan. Frank de Caro was heavily involved in the city’s Italian-American community and founded New York’s Italian Chamber of Commerce. Frank de Caro was also a large supporter of Columbus Day and participated in efforts to have it declared a national holiday. Between 1909 and 1910, de Caro, along with other leaders in the Italian-American community, visited the White House to speak with President William Howard Taft to have Columbus Day legally recognized as a holiday. Their efforts were successful, and Taft declared Columbus Day a national holiday in 1910.
Frank A. de Caro married Anna Menkhoff In 1891. Anna Menkhoff was a German immigrant who had moved to New York with her parents August and Maria Meyer Menkhoff in the 1880s. The Menkhoffs owned and operated a pastry shop in New York, and Anna worked for her parents in the store. When Frank de Caro first started courting Anna Menkhoff, her parents expressed their disapproval and attempted to dissuade their daughter from marrying him. The Menkhoffs went so far as to buy a new piano for Anna as a way to distract their daughter from Frank’s advances. They were ultimately unsuccessful and Frank and Anna eloped in 1891. Frank and Anna de Caro later had the receipt for the piano framed along with a letter Frank wrote to her parents announcing their elopement. The receipt and letter are included in this collection. Frank and Anna de Caro had seven children, Elsa, Francis, Lillyan, Frank E., Gertrude, Arthur, and William de Caro, who died as an infant. The family lived in Brooklyn at 725 Greenwood Avenue.
Frank and Anna de Caro’s son Frank E. de Caro was born in Brooklyn in 1908. During the 1930s Frank E. de Caro worked as a stock broker on Wall Street and as a male model. In 1938 he married his long-time girlfriend Beatrice Mulvehill. Frank and Beatrice met at Lake Waramaug in Connecticut where both of their families spent summer vacations. The couple began dating in 1929, and eventually married in 1938. Frank was drafted during World War II and died in France in 1944. They had one son, Frank de Caro, who was born in 1943.
The Mulvehills were Irish immigrants who moved to Brooklyn in the 1840s. Beatrice’s father John Henry Mulvehill (1873-1943) was born in Brooklyn in 1873 and had a successful career in the insurance business. He married Myrtle Bell Brown (1880-1963) from Russell County, Kansas and the couple had five children, Edward Leslie, John Joseph, Vincent Lyman, Urban Sylvester, and Beatrice Agnes. Many of Mulvehill’s sons also worked in insurance, while their sister Beatrice worked for many years at the Brooklyn Public Library.
Scope and Contents note
This collection contains documents and photographs that relate to three families of European immigrants (from Italy, Germany, and Ireland) who settled in New York City in the late 19th century. The de Caro, Menkhoff, and Mulvehill families became connected in 1891 when Frank A. de Caro married Anna Menkhoff, and in 1939 when their son Frank E. de Caro married Beatrice Mulvehill. While small and incomplete as a family history, this collection spotlights several topics, most notably, Italian-American identity in turn-of-the-century New York City, travel accounts, and middle-class courtship during the Great Depression.
Materials have been arranged into three series. Series I, Correspondence and Family Papers consists primarily of letters written by Frank E. de Caro (Frank A. de Caro’s son) to Beatrice Mulvehill between 1930 and 1933, before they were married. These letters discuss their courtship as well as Frank’s social life in New York and his work as a stock broker during the Depression. There are also several post cards written by Beatrice Mulvehill to her family members during a 1928 trip to Europe with a group of students from Berkeley Institute, (now Berkeley Carroll School in Brooklyn) where Beatrice attended high school. Other papers in this series relate to the first generation of the de Caro family including: documents from Frank A. de Caro’s flag manufacturing company, obituaries and biographical sketches of Frank A. de Caro and his wife Anna Menkhoff de Caro, and an account of her childhood by their daughter Frances de Caro.
Series II, Bound Volumes, contains several catalogues from de Caro’s flag manufacturing company, De Caro’s & D’Angelo Co; scrapbooks, and travel journals. The first scrapbook in this series was compiled by Frank A. de Caro and contains letters to and from a number of Italian organization and dignitaries, which are in Italian. The second scrapbook contains photographs and memorabilia from Frank A. de Caro’s daughter Lillyan de Caro Santo during a 1977 trip to Germany to visit with Menkhoff family relatives. There are also three travel journals documenting various trips to Europe and New England by Frank A. de Caro’s daughters Frances de Caro, Lillyan de Caro Santo, and one by Beatrice Mulvehill (before her marriage to Frank E. de Caro).
Series III, Photographs, spans the period between the 1880s and 1990s depicting several generations of de Caro and Mulvehill family members. These images vary in size and format and include both individual and group photographs. Highlights include tintype portraits, images of the Mulvehill family at Coney Island in the early twentieth century, and a 1910 photograph of Frank A. de Caro with a delegation Italian-Americans meeting with President William Howard Taft at the White House to discuss making Columbus Day a national holiday. Photographs in this series largely depict family events, including holidays, leisure, and travel and reflect these families’ attempt to document their history in the early days of photography.
Arrangement note
This collection has been arranged into series by format. Materials within series are grouped by subject or creator.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Gift of Frank de Caro, 2013.
de Caro, Anna Menkhoff; de Caro, Beatrice Mulvehill; de Caro, Frances; de Caro, Frank A., 1866-1955; de Caro, Frank E., 1908-1944; de Caro, Frank, 1943-; Santo, Lillyan de Caro; Black-and-white photographs; Catalogs; Color photographs; Columbus Day; Correspondence; Courtship.; Europe - Description and Travel; Immigrants--United States--History--19th century; New England–Description and travel; Scrapbooks; Tintypes
- Series I: Correspondence and Family Papers, 1890-1955
  Scope and Contents note
  The bulk of this series consists of correspondence from Frank E. de Caro and his wife Beatrice Mulvehill, which are contained in the first subseries. This series also contains several assorted items related to Frank E. de Caro's parents Frank A. de Caro and Anna Menkhoff de Caro. These items are included in the second subseries.
  - Subseries I.1: Frank E. de Caro and Beatrice Mulvehill Correspondence, 1930-1933
    - Beatrice Mulvehill postcards to her family, 1926 (Box 2, Volume 8)
    - Frank E. de Caro to Beatrice Mulvehill, 1930-1933 (Box 1, Folder 1-7)
  - Subseries I.2: Frank A. de Caro and Anna Menkhoff Family Papers, 1890-1955
    - Partnership agreement establishing De Caro and Abbate (photocopy), 1901 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Letter from Frank A. de Caro to the Parents of Anna Menkhoff, 1891 September 23 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Receipt for a piano bought for Anna Menkhoff by her parents, 1890 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Frank A. de Caro and Anna Menkhoff obituaries and biographical information, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Frances de Caro's account of her childhood, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Political announcement for Elsa de Caro Napolis running for Democratic state committee, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Cartoon by Lillyan de Caro Santo depicting her sister Frances de Caro as a court reporter, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - De Caro & D'Angelo Inc. company envelopes, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Series II: Bound Volumes, 1900
  This series includes travel journals, scrapbooks, and business catalogues from Frank A. de Caro's company De Caro & D'Angelo Co., Inc.
  - Stenna Calendario e Guida degl'Italani in America, 1893 (Box 2, Volume 7)
  - Frank de Caro scrapbook of correspondence with Italian and Italian-American dignitaries and organizations, 1906-1936 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
  - Frances de Caro autograph book, 1910-1918 (Box 2, Volume 9)
  - Frances de Caro travel journal from trip to Europe, 1921 (Box 2, Volume 11)
  - Frances de Carol memorabilia European travel journal, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Passenger List for American Twin Crew Steamship "Republic", 1926 August 24 (Box 2, Volume 3)
  - Beatrice Mulvehill European travel journal, 1926 (Box 2, Volume 1)
  - Frances de Caro New England travel journal (in verse), 1927 (Box 2, Volume 2)
  - Lillyan de Caro Santo travel journal from trip to Europe, 1952 (Box 2, Volume 10)
  - Lillyan de Caro Santo scrapbook of her visit to Germany to see Menkhoff relatives, 1977 (Box 5, Volume 1)
  - Catalogue, No. 15, De Caro and D'Angelo Co., Inc., 1938 (Box 1, Volume 16)
  - Catalogue: "Regulation Equipment for the Equestrian Order S. Gregorii Magni Pro Equitibus Civilius" by De Caro and D'Angelo Co., Inc., undated (Box 2, Volume 4)
  - Catalogue: "Regulation Equipment for the Equestrian Order of the Knights of the Holy Sepulchre of Jerusalem" by De Caro and D'Angelo Co., Inc., undated (Box 2, Volume 5)
  - Catalogo Illustrato, No. 6, Frank de Caro Italo-American Flag Co., undated (Box 2, Volume 6)
- Series III: Photographs, 1880-1970
  Arrangement note
  Photographs have been organized by family, and are generally described at the item level, although there are multiple photogrphs of some subjects.
  - Subseries III.1: Beatrice Mulvehill and Frank de Caro Photographs
    This subseries contains photographs of Beatrice Mulvehill and Frank E. de Caro, singly and together, both before and after their marriage. It also contains photographs of their son Frank de Caro as a child.
    - Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro), undated (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro) at college, circa 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro) European Tour, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro) in St. Mark's Square, Venice with members of her tour group, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro) with her Berkeley school group in the Alps, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro) at the Trevi Fountain in Rome with her European tour group, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Pope Pious XI with whom Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro) had a private audience, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - London hotel for Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro) European tour, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro) first communion, circa 1912 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro), far left, with her class at Georgian Court College, circa 1920-1939 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro), "Fancy dress, Atlantic Crossing", 1926 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Wedding of Beatrice Mulvehill and Frank E. de Caro at Our Lady of Angels Roman Catholic Church in Brooklyn, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Frank E. de Caro and Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro) with friends in his Flatbush apartment, circa 1930-1949 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Frank E. de Caro, possibly at his wedding, circa 1938 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Our Lady of Angels Roman Catholic Church, Brooklyn, NY. Possibly for wedding of Beatrice Mulvehill and Frank E. de Caro., circa 1938 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro) with her European tour group, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill de Caro and Frank E. de Caro at the front door of his family home in Brooklyn, 1944 February 13 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Frank E. de Caro, Beatrice Mulvehill de Caro on desk at his family home in Brooklyn, circa 1940-1949 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Frank de Caro, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Frank de Caro with his father Frank E. de Caro, circa 1944 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Frank de Caro childhood, circa 1940-1959 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Frank de Caro after his return from India, circa 1960-1969 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill de Caro with her son Frank de Caro, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Subseries III.2: Mulvehill Family Photographs
    Photographs within this subseries contain images of a number of individuals in the Mulvehill family. They span several generations and cover a broad time range from the 1880s to the 1990s.
    - Annie C. Brown (Mother of Myrtle Belle Brown Mulvehill), 1934, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Annie C. Brown with several Mulvehill grandsons and others, circa 1880-1910 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Annie C. Brown, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Clarissa Brown, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Barbara Mulvehill (Gray), undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill (Palmer), undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill Palmer bridal portrait, 1956 September 29 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill Palmer and John M. Palmer in some photos with their children, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Edward Leslie Mulvehill, circa 1905 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - John Henry Mulvehill with sons Edward and John at Coney Island (tintype), circa 1900-1910 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - John Henry Mulvehill, circa 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - John Henry Mulvehill, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - John Henry (Jack) Mulvehill, circa 1950-1959 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - John Henry (Jack) Mulvehill, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - John J. Mulvehill at work, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - John J. Mulvehill, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Lillian Firmbach Mulvehill holding great grandchild, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Lillian Firmbach Mulvehill, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Margo Sefton Mulvehill, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Mary Jane Mulvehill, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Mary Nassett Mulvehill, undated (Box 3, Folder 36-37)
    - Myrtle Belle Brown (Mulvehill)at Coney Island with unidentified boyfriend (tintype), circa 1880-1910 (Box 3, Folder 38-39)
    - Myrtle Belle Brown (Mulvehill) and unidentified at Coney Island (Boxed tintype), circa 1880-1910 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Myrtle Belle Brown (Mulvehill) at Coney Island with unidentified friends (tintype), circa 1880-1910 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Myrtle Belle Brown Mulvehill and her son Edward at the wedding of Beatrice Mulvehill de Caro and Frank E. de Caro, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Myrtle Belle Brown Mulvehill with her sister Agnes Brown Wagner and her daughter Beatrice Mulvehill de Caro, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Myrtle Belle Brown Mulvehill and Beatrice Mulvehill de Caro, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Myrtle Belle Brown Mulvehill, probably with great grandchild, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Myrtle Belle Brown Mulvehill probably with her niece Myrtle Brown Schultz O'Toole, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Myrtle Brown Mulvehill, undated (Box 3, Folder 45-46)
    - Urban S. Mulvehill, undated (Box 4, Folder 12-13)
    - Urban S. Mulvehill during World War II, circa 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Urban S. Mulvehill Jr. at his wedding with bride Diane Gregory and parents Margaret Sefton Mulvehill and Urban S. Mulvehill, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Vincent L. Mulvehill, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Vincent L. Mulvehill and John L. Mulvehill with a business group, undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Mulvehill children at Coney Island with their nursemaid and mother, circa 1910 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - John Henry Mulvehill and his son Edward at Coney Island, circa 1910 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro), Brother Urban S. Mulvehill, and dog, circa 1910 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - John Henry Mulvehill, Myrtle Belle Brown Mulvehill, Urban S. Mulvehill and Beatrice Mulvehill de Caro in the Catskills, circa 1910 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - John Henry Mulvehill with son Urban S. Mulvehill and Mr. Evans (Urban's godfather and friend of John Henry) at Luna Park, Coney Island, circa 1912 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Vincent, John, Urban, Edward Mulvehill with other unidentified boys, circa 1912 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - John Henry Mulvehill with his son John and his wife Mary at Coney Island, circa 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Mary Nassett Mulvehill and John J. Mulvehill possibly at Coney Island, circa 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Jack Mulvehill, Frank E. de Caro, Vincent Mulvehill, and Urban S. Mulvehill, circa 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Urban S. Mulvehill, Kevin Mulvehill, Mary Nassett Mulvehill, Mary Jane Mulvehill, possibly Urban S. Jr. Mulvehill and Margo Mulvehill, circa 1950 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Margo Sefton Mulvehill, Urban S. Mulvehill Jr., Margo Mulvehill, Mary Jane Mulvehill, Kevin Mulvehill, and Vera Sexton Mulvehill, circa 1950-1959 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Grays and Palmers, Cleveland, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - John J. Mulvehill with his sister Beatrice Mulvehill de Caro and daughter Jane Mulvehill in Beatrice's Ridge Boulevard apartment, Brooklyn, 1967 January (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Unidentified woman, Vincent L. Mulvehill probably at residence of John and Mary Mulvehill on 73rd Street in Brooklyn, undated (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - John J. Mulvehill and Urban S. Mulvehill, undated (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill Palmer, Lillian Firmbach Mulvehill, and Barbara Mulvehill Gray, undated (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Frank de Caro with his cousin Mary Jane Mulvehill and her friend Nancy Fanelli, undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Cousins Margo, Kevin, and Mary Jane Mulvehill, Frank de Caro, and Urban S. Mulvehill Jr., undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Barbara Mulvehill (Gray) and Beatrice Mulvehill (Palmer) with their cousin (either Jack or Kevin Mulvehill) as children., undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Beach Lake, PA, farm/boarding house where Frank de Caro spent some summers, circa 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Subseries III.3: Mulvehill Family Visits to Lake Waramaug, CT
    This subseries contains photographs of gatherings at the Mulvehill family summer home at Lake Waramaug in Connecticut.
    - Lake Waramaug house interior, circa 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Group on steps of Lake Waramaug house, circa 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 71-72)
    - Group in front of Lake Waramaug house including Mary Nassett Mulvehill, Myrtle Belle Brown Mulvehill, and probably Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro), 1934 September 18 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Group on steps of Lake Waramaug house including Mary Nassett Mulvehill and John J. Mulvehill, 1934 September 18 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Myrtle Belle Brown Mulvehill with group in front of Lake Waramaug house, 1934 September 18 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Group in front of Lake Waramaug House, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Group on steps of Lake Waramaug house, circa 1930-1939 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Lillian Firmbach Mulvehill, Mary Nassett Mulvehill and children at Lake Waramaug, circa 1930-1949 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Myrtle Belle Brown Mulvehill and her daughter Beatrice Mulvehill (de Caro) in front of Lake Waramaug house, circa 1930-1949 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Mulvehill family Thanksgiving, Lake Waramaug, CT, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Lake Waramaug, CT, 1996 November (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Myrtle Belle Brown Mulvehill on her lawn of Lake Waramaug house with her dog, undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Unidentified, Vincent Mulvehill, and John Mulvehill, at Lake Waramaug house, winter, undated (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Boathouse, Lake Waramaug, CT (build by John Henry Mulvehill), undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Lake Waramaug house, undated (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
  - Subseries III.4: de Caro Family Photographs
    Photographs in this series largely document two generations of de Caros between the 1880s and 1940s. It also contains several assorted images of later generations of de Caros in the last half of the 20th century.
    - Sherman Beattie and Joan McAlevey Beattie with their son Richard, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Anna Menkhoff (de Caro), dressed for a costume ball (framed tintype), circa 1880-1900 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Anna Menkhoff de Caro, circa 1880-1900 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Anna Menkhoff de Caro in Lakeville, CT, 1944, undated (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Anna Menkhoff de Caro with Lillyan de Caro Santo, John Santo, Frances de Caro in her living room at 725 Greenwood Ave, Brooklyn, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Anna Menkhoff de Caro, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Anna Menkhoff de Caro in her living room, circa 1970-1979 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Anna Menkhoff de Caro, undated (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Anna Menkhoff de Caro and Frank A. de Caro in Monroe, NY, undated (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Anna Menkhoff de Caro and Frank A. de Caro, undated (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Arthur de Caro (Died 1920s), undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Arthur de Caro, first communion, circa 1900-1920 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Beatrice Mulvehill de Caro, circa 1920s-1939 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Frances de Caro in Italy, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Frances de Caro in Saint Marks Square in Venice, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Frances Antoinette de Caro with her father Frank A. de Caro after their return to New York from Europe aboard the S.S. Adriatic., 1921 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Captain of the ship that took Frances de Caro and Frank A. de Caro to Italy, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Frances de Caro, circa 1920-1929 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Frances de Caro, undated (Box 3, Folder 98-99)
    - Boxed portrait of Frank A. de Caro, circa 1880-1900 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Frank A. de Caro in uniform of Italian-American organization identified as "Francisco De Caro", circa 1880-1900 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Frank A. de Caro with uniformed Italian-American organization in New York, undated (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Frank A. de Caro in front of his business on W. 34th Street in New York, circa 1880-1900 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Frank A. de Caro in Arizona, circa 1900-1920 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Frank A. de Caro at Niagara Falls, circa 1900-1920 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Frank A. de Caro with a delegation of Italian-American leaders at the White House with President Taft. They had gone to discuss making Columbus Day a national holiday, circa 1910 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Frank A. de Caro in Italy, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Frank A. de Caro and his daughter Frances in Saint Marks Square, Venice, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Frank A. de Caro and his daughter Frances aboard the ship that took them to Italy, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 106)